[
 {
            "question": "Who wrote The Odyssey?",
            "a": "Socrates",
            "b": "Plato",
            "c": "Homer",
            "d": "Shakespeare",
            "correct answer": "c",
            "subject": "Literature"
    },

    {
            "question": "What is the first item in the periodic table of elements?",
            "a": "Hydrogen",
            "b": "Sodium",
            "c": "Helium",
            "d": "Aluminum",
            "correct answer" : "a",
            "subject": "Science"
    },

    {
            "question": "At the Second Continental Congress, who was elected General of the Continental Army?",
            "a": "John Adams",
            "b": "Benjamin Franklin",
            "c": "Samuel Davis",
            "d": "George Washington",
            "correct answer": "d",
            "subject": "History"
    },

    {
            "question": "Who was the ruler of Germany during the first World War?",
            "a": "Helmuth von Moltke",
            "b": "Friedrich Wilhelm",
            "c": "Manfred Richtoffen",
            "d": "Erich Ludendorff",
            "correct answer": "b",
            "subject": "History"

    },

    {
            "question": "In which group of people were the first ones to celebrate Thanksgiving?",
            "a": "Free Masons",
            "b": "Quakers",
            "c": "Pilgrims",
            "d": "Native Americans",
            "correct answer": "c",
            "subject": "History"
    },

    {
            "question": "What ancient civilization built the Machu Pichu in Peru?",
            "a": "The Aztecs",
            "b": "The Mayans",
            "c": "The Incas",
            "d": "The Egyptians",
            "correct answer": "c",
            "subject": "Geography"
    },

    {
            "question": "In which year did Thomas Edison invent the light bulb?",
            "a": "1879",
            "b": "1775",
            "c": "1895",
            "d": "1913",
            "correct answer": "a",
            "subject": "History"
    },

    {
            "question": "Name a famous emperor of the Roman Empire?",
            "a": "Spartacus",
            "b": "Otto Octavius",
            "c": "Julius Caesar",
            "d": "Pontius Pilate",
            "correct answer": "c",
            "subject": "History"
    },

    {
            "question": "The first day of the 20th century was...",
            "a": "January 1st, 1801",
            "b": "January 1st, 1901",
            "c": "January 1st, 2001",
            "d": "January 1st, 2011",
            "correct answer": "b",
            "subject": "History"
    },
    {
            "question": "Is Australia considered an island?",
            "a": "Yes, because it is surrounded by water",
            "b": "Yes, because it is surrounded by three oceans",
            "c": "No, a continent cannot be considered an island",
            "d": "No, it has too many diverse biomes",
            "correct answer": "c",
            "subject": "Geography"
    },
    {
            "question": "Which one of these Hololives are not part of Gen 3?",
            "a": "Houshou Marine",
            "b": "Shiranui Flare",
            "c": "Shirakami Fubuki",
            "d": "Shirogane Noel",
            "correct answer": "c",
            "subject": "Hololive"
    }
 ]
 
 